{
"question": "忙しい",
"answer": "いそがしい"
},
{
"question": "両親",
"answer": "りょうしん"
},
{
"question": "泳ぐ",
"answer": "およぐ"
},
{
"question": "出す",
"answer": "だす"
},
{
"question": "立つ",
"answer": "たつ"
},
{
"question": "早い",
"answer": "はやい"
},
{
"question": "楽しい",
"answer": "たのしい"
},
{
"question": "面白い",
"answer": "おもしろい"
},
{
"question": "絵",
"answer": "え"
},
{
"question": "女の子",
"answer": "おんなのこ"
},
{
"question": "着る",
"answer": "きる"
},
{
"question": "上手",
"answer": "じょうず"
},
{
"question": "古い",
"answer": "ふるい"
},
{
"question": "強い",
"answer": "つよい"
},
{
"question": "全部",
"answer": "ぜんぶ"
},
{
"question": "呼ぶ",
"answer": "よぶ"
},
{
"question": "午後",
"answer": "ごご"
},
{
"question": "掛ける",
"answer": "かける"
},
{
"question": "辞書",
"answer": "じしょ"
},
{
"question": "天気",
"answer": "てんき"
},
